[{"question":"# Q1. You want to schedule a cron job to send a message to a Cloud Pub/Sub topic hourly. What do you do?","options":["Create a Cloud Function with a targer of HTTP","Create a Cloud Scheduler job with a targer of HTTP","Create a Cloud Function with a targer of Cloud Pub/Sub","Create a Cloud Scheduler job with a targer of Cloud Pub/Sub"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Create a Cloud Function with a targer of Cloud Pub/Sub"},{"question":"# Q2. You want to set up a managed Apache Spark cluster. Which service do you configure?","options":["Cloud Dataprep","Cloud Composer","Cloud Dataflow","Cloud Dataproc"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Cloud Dataproc"},{"question":"# Q3. GCP Organizations are not available in your GCP project. What type of account are you using?","options":["Temporary","Free Tier- free trail doesnt have the organization","Local","Organizational"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Free Tier- free trail doesnt have the organization"},{"question":"# Q4. What feature do you need to enable to support load balancing and autoscaling managed instance groups for Compute Engine?","options":["metadata","security scans","network endpoint groups","health checks"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"health checks"},{"question":"# Q5. You are designing an application that will send messages with the MQTT protocol. What service should you use?","options":["BigQuery","Cloud Pub/Sub","IoT Broker","Bigtable"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Cloud Pub/Sub"},{"question":"# Q6. You want to configure services to host a mobile application that uses TensorFlow Lite models. Which services should you use?","options":["Cloud Functions and ML Kit","Firebase and AI Platform jobs","Firebase and ML Kit","Cloud Functions and AI Platform jobs"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Firebase and ML Kit"},{"question":"# Q7. You need to deploy Redis with unique persistent identities and stable hostnames on GKE. What type of deployment object do you use?","options":["GCP deployment","YAML configuration file","Python nested template","stateful set"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"YAML configuration file"},{"question":"# Q8. You want to try out a machine-learning TensorFlow example notebook with the fewest configuration steps on GCP. What do you do?","options":["Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator to use GPU.","Create a notebook instance with TPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","Create a notebook instance with GPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator yo use TPU."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Create a notebook instance with TPU. Upload the notebook to the instance."},{"question":"# Q9. You need to configure a data retention policy for a Cloud Storage bucket to govern how long objects in the bucket must be retained. What feature do you enable?","options":["Requester Pays","Bucket Lock","Bucket Policy Only","Encryption Type"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Bucket Lock"},{"question":"# Q10. To be able to configure an existing Cloud Function, what information should you review and from which location?","options":["execution time in Cloud Storage logs","execution time in Stackdriver logs","text payload in Stackdriver logs","text payload in Cloud Storage logs"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"text payload in Stackdriver logs"},{"question":"# Q11. You need to execute a \"lift and shift\" move with as few steps as possible. Which items do you need to create to accomplish this task, listed in the correct order of creation?","options":["1. Create a VPN from GCP to your corporate network.","      2. Create a GCP network for the project.","      3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","1. Create a GCP network for the project.","      2. Create a VPN from your corporate network to GCP.","      3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","1. Create a GCP network for the project. ","      2. Create a VPN from GCP to your corporate network. ","      3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","1. Create a VPN from your corporate network to GCP.","      2. Create a GCP network for the project.","      3. Create the VM instances to support the application."],"anwserIndex":6,"answerText":"1. Create a GCP network for the project. "},{"question":"# Q12. You are concerned about data egress charges for files in a Cloud Storage bucket. What configuration change should you make?","options":["Enable Requester Pays on the project.","Enable Requester Pays on the bucket.","Change the default storage class from multi-regional to regional.","Change the default storage class from regional to multi-regional."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Change the default storage class from multi-regional to regional."},{"question":"# Q13. You need to troubleshoot an Android app that uses Cloud Storage. Where do you look for logs?","options":["Firebase Crashlytics","Firebase Crashlytics and Stackdriver","Firebase Testlab and Stackdriver","Stackdriver"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Firebase Crashlytics and Stackdriver"},{"question":"# Q14. You want to configure services to be able to perform a regular interactive query of Google AdWords data. What should you do?","options":["Plan to use BigQuery. Create a BigQuery data set to hold the data.","Plan to use Cloud SQL. Enable Cloud SQL Transfer Data API.","Plan to use Cloud SQL. Create a Cloud SQL Database to hold the data.","Plan to user BigQuery. Enable BigQuery Transfer Data API."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Plan to user BigQuery. Enable BigQuery Transfer Data API."},{"question":"# Q15. You want to use GCP-preferred base container images. Where can your users find these images?","options":["Docker Hub","Compute Engine base images","GCP Marketplace","Google Kubernetes Engine base images"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"GCP Marketplace"},{"question":"# Q16. You want to set a notification for service spend in GCP. What do you do, and who will be notified?","options":["Use the GCP Billing console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The billing admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","Use the GCP Billing console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The organizational admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","Use the GCP Organizational console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The project admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","Use the GCP Organizational console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The organizational admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded."],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Use the GCP Billing console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The billing admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded."},{"question":"# Q17. Cloud SQL supports which two relational databases?","options":["Radis and Oracle","MySQL and Oracle","Radis and PostgreSQL","MySQL and PostgreSQL"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"MySQL and PostgreSQL"},{"question":"# Q18. You want to try out a machine-learning TensorFlow example notebook with the fewest configuration steps on GCP. What do you do?","options":["Create a notebook instance with TPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","Create a notebook instance with GPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator to use GPU.","Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator to use TPU."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Create a notebook instance with GPU. Upload the notebook to the instance."},{"question":"# Q19. You want to quickly test a single Docker container image that will start a stateless HTTP service on GCP. Which service do you select to host your container image?","options":["Cloud Run","Cloud Run on Google Kubernetes Engine","Cloud Functions","Google Kubernetes Engine"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Google Kubernetes Engine"},{"question":"# Q20. You want to develop Firebase security rules following Google best practices. Which tool(s) do you use?","options":["Firebase Emulator","Firebase Emulator and GCP Rules Simulator","GCP policy emulator and Firebase Rules Simulator","Firebase Emulator and Firebase Rules Simulator"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Firebase Emulator"},{"question":"# Q21. You want to build an application with conversation interpretation based on machine learning speech understanding. Which service is a best fit for this scenario?","options":["Dialogflow","Natural Language Translation","Speech API","AutoML Natural Language"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Dialogflow"},{"question":"# Q22. Which service must you enable on your GKE cluster in order to use Cloud Run on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE)?","options":["Stackdriver","Istio","Knative","Spinnaker"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Stackdriver"},{"question":"# Q23. How can you enable clients inside a GKE cluster to be able to contact Pods?","options":["Configure the clients to connect via the default cluster IP.","Configure an external name. Configure the clients to connect via the external name.","Configure a node port. COnfigure the clients to connect via the node port.","Configure a load balancer. Configure the clients to connect via the load balancer."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Configure a node port. COnfigure the clients to connect via the node port."},{"question":"# Q24. You want to capture the message acknowledgment state of a subscription at a given time. What do you do?","options":["Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription backup.","Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription topic.","Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription snapshot.","Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription snapshot."},{"question":"# Q25. You need to set a bucket storage class for data that will be accessed once a month or less. Which type do you select?","options":["coldline","multi-regional","regional","nearline"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"nearline"},{"question":"# Q26. Which command copies a file named test.txt to a Cloud Storage bucket named myBucket?","options":["gcloud cp gs://myBucket test.txt","gsutil cp gs://myBucket test.txt","gcloud cp test.txt gs://myBucket","gsutil cp test.txt gs://myBucket"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"gsutil cp test.txt gs://myBucket"},{"question":"# Q27. Which command adds a column family named `cf1` to your Bigtable table named `my-table`?","options":["cbt createfamily cf1 my-table","cbt createfamily my-table cf1","gcloud createfamily cf1 my-table cf1","gcloud createfamily my-table cf1"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"cbt createfamily my-table cf1"}]